[TOHKA] ♪ Taking care to
keep my baggage with me ♪
♪ Loading more and more when I
should be unloading ♪
♪ Always seem to
repeat my mistakes ♪
♪ Just to save my own pride ♪
♪ I'll go on ignoring
all of my faults ♪
♪ Spreading rumors
about everybody else ♪
♪ But I don't feel
so great about it ♪
♪ Going through the motions ♪
♪ Robotic tic and tac ♪
♪ "Go for it," they say ♪
♪ But how do I? ♪
♪ Attention! ♪
♪ I seem to be caught up
in a mess of things ♪
♪ Is the grass much greener ♪
♪ When on the other side? ♪
♪ Yes and no, yes and no ♪
♪ The moment I finally
stopped and looked around ♪
♪ When time was stilled
then I could clearly see ♪
‐‐♪ in color ♪
‐‐Dammit!
What in the world are you?
Tell me!
[song continues]
[CROWD cheering]